neosounds.com 2006-12-21

# Privacy Policy

|      **ROYALTY FREE MUSIC CDs**  
---  
  
     **SOUND EFFECTS**

This site requires  
Macromedia Flash Player

| **WE RESPECT YOUR PRIVACY**  
---  
  
**What information do we collect and how do we use it?**  
We collect and use your personal information ONLY for processing your order(s). Any personal data you provide us including and similar to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of NEO Sounds. We here at NEO Sounds do not collect and never get to see any credit card details. Visitor are redirected to a secure server of reliable online payment system before transfering credit card data. ([more info about payment process](http://www.neosounds.com/?mod=info&modfile=ordering_info)).

**How Do We Protect Your Information?**  
We use industry-standard encryption technologies when transmitting and receiving your personal data. We have security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of information that we have collected from or about you.

**Cookies**  
"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Cookies allow us to recognize you each time you visit this site. Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information. We use cookies to store visitors preferences, record session information, such as items that visitors add to their shopping cart, customize Web page content based on visitors' browser type or other information that the visitor sends.

**External Sites.**  
NEO Sounds is not responsible for the content of external internet sites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information.

**Questions**  
If you have any questions about your privacy when using this website, or concerning our's use of personal information, please contact us: [info@neosounds.com](mailto:info@neosounds.com)  

© Copyright 2004-2006 [NEO Sounds LLC](http://www.neosounds.com/). All rights reserved.Sound Effects, Royalty Free Music Loops  
Free Background Music for Web Page, Free Music Loops  
Production Music Library, [Royalty Free Music](http://www.neosounds.com/?mod=royalty-free-music&category_id=1 "Royalty Free Music")
